UNITE Audio-Visual Collection 6000 AV
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- ABC - Phyllis Burns interview, 8 (Box 17)
- Cavanaugh's Corner - 12/4/1997 - GUESS What?, 9 (Box 17)
- District Mtg - 9/6/1997 - Anti-NAFFA Rally, 10 (Box 17)
- Maine Watch about Hathaway, 11 (Box 17)
- AFL-CIO Strategic Media Campaign ADS, 12 (Box 17)
- Fojtosek Ratification (reel 3), 13 (Box 17)
- Fojtosek Ratification (reel 1), 14 (Box 17)
- Fojtosek Ratification (reel 2), 15 (Box 17)
- Pre-Apprentice - MWT - 1996, 16 (Box 17)
- #3 Workers Rights Hearing - Feb. 18, 1999, Miami at Caleb Center, 17 (Box 17)
- #2 Workers Rights Hearing, Feb. 18, 1999, Miami at Caleb Center, 18 (Box 17)
- #1Workers Rights Hearing, Feb. 18, 1999, Miami at Caleb Center, 19 (Box 17)
- November 22, 1999, 20 (Box 17)
  ch.7 - Eyewitness News
- ESPN - Ch. 8 Outside the Lines - Made in Vietnam (sneaker sweatshop), 21 (Box 17)
- May 27, 1968, Afternoon, 1 (Box 18)
- May 27, 1968, Morning - Financial report, 2 (Box 18)
- UNITE, Jay Mazur Retirement Video - 6/26/2001, 12 (Box 18)
- Evy Duty, 13 (Box 18)
- What Happened to the American Dream?, 14 (Box 18)
- Its time to say yes to Dukakis, 15 (Box 18)
- Solidarity Day March, Washington, DC, 16 (Box 18)
- What happened to the American Dream?, 17 (Box 18)
- AFL-CIO, Immigration, Cathy Wallder, 18 (Box 18)
- American Bar Ass., Legalization Appeals, tape 2, 19 (Box 18)
- American Bar Assn., Legalization Appeals, tape 1, 20 (Box 18)
- J. Ian Morrison and Robert Johansen at Apple University, Speakers Forum, 3/93 on Issues and Trends for Business and Government, 1993; 21 (Box 18)
- The Golden Door, presented by the New York Joint Board, ACTWU, 22 (Box 18)
- Moyers/Minimum Wages, 23 (Box 18)
- Take the Power, from the Creators of One Fine Day, 24 (Box 18)
- Immigration, Midday Liver over WNEW-TV, NY, 1984; 25 (Box 18)
  Wednesday, June 20, 1984
- Triangle Fire and Interview with Leon Stien, 5/27/1986, 26 (Box 18)
- Immigration Control Bill, Eyewitness News, WABC-TV, June 15, Friday, 27 (Box 18)
- ILGWU, Department of Labor, Hall of Fame, 1993, 28 (Box 18)
- Aliens, WNBC-TV, Phil Donahue, Wed, Mar 18 at 9 AM, 29 (Box 18)
- Breaking the Silence; The Fight for Justice at Peerless, 31 (Box 18)
- Bruce Raynor in the Southern Region: Unite!, 1998; 32 (Box 18)
- Whiteville Apparel Together: Local 1077 - UNITE (Box 19)
  - Whiteville Apparel Together: Local 1077 - UNITE, 1 (Box 19)
- Yes! Send me a year's subscription to Newstrack Executive Tape Service, 1 (Box 20)
- Listen, It's easy to master today's top business books in minutes!, 1 (Box 21)
- Unlabeled, 1 (Box 22)
- 4/23/1987 - ILGWU - Imm Seminar, tape 2, 1 (Box 23)
- 4/23/1987, ILGWU, Immi Seminar, tape 1, 1 (Box 24)
- 4/22/1987, ILGWU - Immi Seminar, tape 2, 1 (Box 25)
- 4/21/1987 - ILGWU, Immi Seminar, tape 4; 4/22/1987, tape 1, 1 (Box 26)
- 4/22/1987 - ILGWU - Immi Seminar, tape 3, 1 (Box 27)
- 4/121/1987 - ILGWU - Immi Seminar, tape 3, 1 (Box 28)
- Whiteville Apparel Together, Local 1077, 1 (Box 29)
  was housed in Media Case in Rm 515, removed and re-housed in box 18 with other cassettes
- AFL-CIO Black South African Workers fund, 1 (Box 30)
  6000 AV #5
- Affiliating With Your Central Labor Council, 1 (Box 31)
  6000 AV #6
- American Cabinet Unites, 1 (Box 32)
  6000 AV #7
- Segment on American Unions, World News Tonight, 9/5/1994, 1 (Box 33)
  6000 AV #8
- Flambeau Airmold Workers: Be Encouraged, 1 (Box 34)
  6000 AV #9
- British Broadcasting Company, Undercover Investigation of the Walt Disney Company in Haiti, 1997; 1 (Box 35)
  Air date: October 1997 --- 6000 AV #10
- CBS Morning News - Monday May 16th (Home Work), 1 (Box 36)
- CBS Morning News - Monday May 16th (Home Work), 1 (Box 37)
  6000 AV #11 (copy 2)
- Clothing Worker; Imported Clothing; Squier/Eskew Communications - 2/5/1988, 1 (Box 38)
  6000 AV #12
- El Monte Workers Lawsuit -- 1.Marketplace PRI, 9/5/1995; 2.KFWB-AM, 9/5/1995; 3.KNX-AM, 9/5/1995, 1 (Box 39)
  6000 AV #71
- Kathie Lee Clothing Sweatshops, 1 (Box 40)
  6000 AV #72
- Gheto and Demilly - 11/28/1989, 1 (Box 41)